{
  "sheet_name": "COVERCARB_50_LV_72",
  "bubble_id": "1708092850246x715931535684665300",
  "supabase_id": "20935c02-278b-4c70-b767-2a58f862f6c3",
  "total_answers": 123,
  "answers": [
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain per- or polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFAS), defined as substances that contain at least one fully fluorinated methyl (CF3-) or methylene (-CF2-) carbon atom (without any H/Cl/Br/I atom attached to it), in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w)?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Product Description or Chemical Characterization ",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Single text line",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Ground Calcium Carbonate Slurry"
    },
    {
      "question": "Product Code/Reference",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Single text line",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "COVERCARB 50 - LV 72%"
    },
    {
      "question": "Function in Application",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Single text line",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Filler or coating pigment"
    },
    {
      "question": "Producer",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Single text line",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Suomen Karbonaatti OY"
    },
    {
      "question": "Production sites",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Single text line",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Suomen Karbon, Lappeenranta, Finland"
    },
    {
      "question": "Add disclaimer (optional)",
      "question_number": "1.1.338",
      "response_type": "Multiple text lines",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "This statement does not remove the obligation of the manufacturer to test the finished product under the above mentioned regulations and standards, if required, and to check compliance to any other applicable provisions for use in contact with food.\n\nOmya, to the best of its knowledge, believes that the information provided above is accurate and correct, based on the sources available at the time of writing. Omya does not assume liability for the use of the information or claims or damages from any third party.\n\nAll the information provided in this form is strictly confidential and for the only purpose of regulatory compliance."
    },
    {
      "question": "2012/481/EU: Commission Decision of 16 August 2012 establishing the ecological criteria for the award of the EU Ecolabel for printed paper:\t\t\t",
      "question_number": "2.1.1",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes, the product meets the criteria. Declaration is available on request."
    },
    {
      "question": "2014/256/EU: Commission Decision of 2 May 2014 establishing the ecological criteria for the award of the EU Ecolabel for converted paper products:\t\t\t",
      "question_number": "2.1.2",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Commission Decision (EU) 2019/70 - ANNEX I of 11 January 2019 establishing the EU Ecolabel criteria for graphic paper:\t\t\t",
      "question_number": "2.1.3",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Commission Decision (EU) 2019/70 - ANNEX II of 11 January 2019 establishing the EU Ecolabel criteria for tissue paper:\t\t\t",
      "question_number": "2.1.4",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Paper Products - Chemical Module",
      "question_number": "2.2.5",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tissue Paper - Supplementary Module",
      "question_number": "2.2.6",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Grease-proof paper - Supplementary Module",
      "question_number": "2.2.7",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Packaging for Liquid Foods",
      "question_number": "2.2.8",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable."
    },
    {
      "question": "Disposables for Food",
      "question_number": "2.2.9",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "DE-UZ-5. Sanitary paper products made of recycled paper",
      "question_number": "2.3.11",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "DE-UZ 14a - Recycled paper",
      "question_number": "2.3.12",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "DE-UZ 14b - Finished products made from recovered paper for office and school demand\t\t\t",
      "question_number": "2.3.13",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "DE-UZ 56 - Recycled cardboard\t\t\t",
      "question_number": "2.3.14",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "DE-UZ 72 - Printing and publication papers",
      "question_number": "2.3.15",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "According to Regulation (EU) No. 528/2012 does the product contain biocidal active substances either intentionally added or non-intentionally via other raw materials?\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can the product be used for production of food contact articles from paper and paperboard (incl. incidental food contact)?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please specify general limitations which may apply to the product (e.g. dosage limitation): (Enter n/a if not applicable)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Multiple text lines",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "See the rest of the document for specific limitations."
    },
    {
      "question": "Can the product be used for the production of articles from paper and paperboard, which comply with the requirements of article 3 and article 17 of the Framework Regulation (EC) No 1935/2004?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "BfR (Federal Institute for Risk Assessment) recommendation XIV. Polymer Dispersions in its current version",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "BfR (Federal Institute for Risk Assessment) recommendation XXXVI. Paper and Board for Food Contact in its current version.\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions: (XXXVI)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 1,
      "row_id": "1708098269689x338384282635730940",
      "answer": "9003-04-7"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions: (XXXVI)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "FCM Number of Regulation, if any",
      "column_order": 2,
      "row_id": "1708098269689x338384282635730940",
      "answer": "BfR XXXVI. B.V.12"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions: (XXXVI)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Chemical name",
      "column_order": 6,
      "row_id": "1708098269689x338384282635730940",
      "answer": "Sodium, polyacrylic acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions: (XXXVI)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions and specifications",
      "column_order": 7,
      "row_id": "1708098269689x338384282635730940",
      "answer": "max. 0.5%"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions: (XXXVI)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Comments",
      "column_order": 8,
      "row_id": "1708098269689x338384282635730940",
      "answer": "Product complies with the limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "BfR (Federal Institute for Risk Assessment) recommendation XXXVI/1. Cooking Papers, Hot Filter Papers and Filter Layers in its current version.",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "BfR (Federal Institute for Risk Assessment) recommendation XXXVI/2. Paper and Paperboard for Baking Purposes in its current version.\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions (XXXVI/2):",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 1,
      "row_id": "1708098702768x337706792291663900",
      "answer": "9003-04-7"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions (XXXVI/2):",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "FCM Number of Regulation, if any",
      "column_order": 2,
      "row_id": "1708098702768x337706792291663900",
      "answer": "BfR Recommendation XXXVI/2. II.E.9"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions (XXXVI/2):",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Chemical Name",
      "column_order": 5,
      "row_id": "1708098702768x337706792291663900",
      "answer": "Sodium, polyacrylic acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions (XXXVI/2):",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions and specifications",
      "column_order": 6,
      "row_id": "1708098702768x337706792291663900",
      "answer": "max. 0.5%"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details for components with restrictions (XXXVI/2):",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Comments",
      "column_order": 7,
      "row_id": "1708098702768x337706792291663900",
      "answer": "Product complies with the limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "BfR (Federal Institute for Risk Assessment) recommendation XXXVI/3. Absorber pads based on cellulosic fibres for food packaging in its current version.",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product comply with the requirements of Commodities Act (Packaging and Consumer Articles) Regulation [Warenwetregeling verpakkingen en gebruiksartikelen] as amended, Hoofdstuk II \"Papier en Karton (Paper and paperboard)\"?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product comply with the requirements of Commodities Act (Packaging and Consumer Articles) Regulation [Warenwetregeling verpakkingen en gebruiksartikelen] as amended; Hoofdstuk X \"Deklagen (Coatings)\"?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product comply with SR 817.023.21 „Ordinance of the EDI on articles and materials for food contact“ of 01 May 2017, especially Annex 10 „Authorized substances for the manufacture of printing inks“?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions, as well as all limitations given in column 7-9:\t\n*Include \"use\" from column 5 and classification (A or B) from column 6.\t\n\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 1,
      "row_id": "1708417501670x195335494463651840",
      "answer": null
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions, as well as all limitations given in column 7-9:\t\n*Include \"use\" from column 5 and classification (A or B) from column 6.\t\n\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "FCM Number of Regulation, if any",
      "column_order": 2,
      "row_id": "1708417501670x195335494463651840",
      "answer": "5035"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions, as well as all limitations given in column 7-9:\t\n*Include \"use\" from column 5 and classification (A or B) from column 6.\t\n\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "SML (mg/kg)",
      "column_order": 3,
      "row_id": "1708417501670x195335494463651840",
      "answer": "6 (expressed as acrylic acid)"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions, as well as all limitations given in column 7-9:\t\n*Include \"use\" from column 5 and classification (A or B) from column 6.\t\n\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Chemical name",
      "column_order": 5,
      "row_id": "1708417501670x195335494463651840",
      "answer": " Polyacrylic acid, salts"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions, as well as all limitations given in column 7-9:\t\n*Include \"use\" from column 5 and classification (A or B) from column 6.\t\n\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions & specifications",
      "column_order": 6,
      "row_id": "1708417501670x195335494463651840",
      "answer": "SML 6 mg/kg (expressed as acrylic acid)"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product comply with the Ministerial Decree of 21 March 1973 (as amended) concerning hygiene requirements for packages, containers and tools destined to come into contact with food or substances for personal use?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product comply with the French Decree No. 2008/1469 of 30 December 2008 „on materials and articles intended to contact with food“? ",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are components used in the manufacture of the product, which are listed with specific limits in the EU Regulation on plastics materials and articles (EU) 10/2011 as amended?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide FCM No. and all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 4,
      "row_id": "1708418980517x363410000116449300",
      "answer": null
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide FCM No. and all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "FCM Number in (EU) 10/2011",
      "column_order": 5,
      "row_id": "1708418980517x363410000116449300",
      "answer": "21"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide FCM No. and all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "E-no",
      "column_order": 7,
      "row_id": "1708418980517x363410000116449300",
      "answer": "E170"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide FCM No. and all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Substance or product (chemical) name",
      "column_order": 8,
      "row_id": "1708418980517x363410000116449300",
      "answer": "Calcium Carbonate (listed as carbonic acid salts)"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can the product be used for the manufacture of food contact articles made from paper and paper board otherwise complying with 21 CFR § 176.170 “Components of paper and paperboard in contact with aqueous and fatty foods”?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.170)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 4,
      "row_id": "1708419354406x198930081644544000",
      "answer": "9003-04-7"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.170)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Substance or product (Chemical) Name",
      "column_order": 5,
      "row_id": "1708419354406x198930081644544000",
      "answer": "Sodium polyacrylate"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.170)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions on food types and/or conditions of use",
      "column_order": 6,
      "row_id": "1708419354406x198930081644544000",
      "answer": "All food types including infant formula and huma milk; All conditions of use"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.170)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions and specifications",
      "column_order": 7,
      "row_id": "1708419354406x198930081644544000",
      "answer": "as a pigment dispersant, contains less than 0.2 percent residual monomer and used at a level not to exceed 2 percent by weight of the paper and paperboard."
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.170)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Comments",
      "column_order": 8,
      "row_id": "1708419354406x198930081644544000",
      "answer": "PNC 002898\nProduct complies with the limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can the product be used for the manufacture of food contact articles made from paper and paper board otherwise complying with 21 CFR § 176.180 “Components of paper and paperboard in contact with dry foods”?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.180)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 4,
      "row_id": "1708419696740x837408109290586100",
      "answer": "9003-04-7"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.180)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Substance or product (Chemical) Name",
      "column_order": 5,
      "row_id": "1708419696740x837408109290586100",
      "answer": "Sodium polyacrylate"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.180)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions on food types and/or conditions of use",
      "column_order": 6,
      "row_id": "1708419696740x837408109290586100",
      "answer": "All food types including infant formula and huma milk; All conditions of use"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.180)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions and specifications",
      "column_order": 7,
      "row_id": "1708419696740x837408109290586100",
      "answer": "as a pigment dispersant, contains less than 0.2 percent residual monomer and used at a level not to exceed 2 percent by weight of the paper and paperboard."
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions: (USA 21 CFR 176.180)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Comments",
      "column_order": 8,
      "row_id": "1708419696740x837408109290586100",
      "answer": "PNC 002898\nProduct complies with the limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "21 CFR § 175.105 “Adhesives”, provided that the respective use conditions described in § 175.105 are met?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "21 CFR § 175.300 “Resinous and polymeric coatings”?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "21 CFR § 176.300 “Slimicides”?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "21 CFR § 176.200 “Defoaming agents used in coatings”?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "21 CFR § 176.210 “Defoaming agents used in the manufacture of paper and paperboard”?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product have a Food Contact Notification (FCN) in effect?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is the product in accordance with the  “National food safety standard – General safety requirements of food contact materials and articles” GB 4806.1-2016 as amended?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does your product fulfill the requirements of the “National Food Safety Standard – Papers, Paperboard Materials and its Articles for Food Contact” GB4806.8-2016 as amended?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does your product comply with the requirements for food contact paper and board materials and their products according to the National Standard of the People's Republic of China GB9685-2016 (Standard for uses of Additives in Food Contact Materials and Articles), issued Oct. 19th 2016 as amended?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions (GB9685)\n",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 4,
      "row_id": "1708420905192x814368683494473700",
      "answer": "9003-04-7"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions (GB9685)\n",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "FCA number of regulation, if any",
      "column_order": 5,
      "row_id": "1708420905192x814368683494473700",
      "answer": "0202"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions (GB9685)\n",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Chemical name",
      "column_order": 8,
      "row_id": "1708420905192x814368683494473700",
      "answer": "2-Propenoic acid, homopolymer, sodium salt"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions (GB9685)\n",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions & specifications",
      "column_order": 9,
      "row_id": "1708420905192x814368683494473700",
      "answer": "Max use level 0.5%\nSML(T) 6 mg/kg (expressed as acrylic acid)"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please give all relevant restrictions (GB9685)\n",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Comments",
      "column_order": 10,
      "row_id": "1708420905192x814368683494473700",
      "answer": "Product complies with the maximum use limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Other Standard (GB) for resin or any positive listing for resin by MOH Announcement which applies to the product?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can the product be used for the production of articles from paper and paperboard, which comply with the requirements of MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 03/92?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 39/19 - Technical regulations on positive list of additives for plastic materials and polymeric coatings intended to contact food, in its current version?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable."
    },
    {
      "question": "MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 40/15 - Technical regulations on materials, packages and cellulosic equipment destined to be in contact with foods, in its current version?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "(40-15) If yes, please give all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 4,
      "row_id": "1708421251271x311918744155717600",
      "answer": null
    },
    {
      "question": "(40-15) If yes, please give all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Chemical name",
      "column_order": 8,
      "row_id": "1708421251271x311918744155717600",
      "answer": "Sodium polyacrylate"
    },
    {
      "question": "(40-15) If yes, please give all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions & specifications",
      "column_order": 9,
      "row_id": "1708421251271x311918744155717600",
      "answer": "Maximum limit 0.5% dry fiber basis"
    },
    {
      "question": "(40-15) If yes, please give all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Comments",
      "column_order": 10,
      "row_id": "1708421251271x311918744155717600",
      "answer": "Product complies with the limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 41/15 - Technical regulations on cellulosic materials for hot cooking and filtration, in its current version?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 42/15 - Technical regulations on materials, containers and cellulosic equipment destined to be in contact with food during cooking or heating in an oven, in its current version?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "(MERC42/15) If yes, please give all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number, if any",
      "column_order": 4,
      "row_id": "1708421856107x309955773281075200",
      "answer": "9003-04-7"
    },
    {
      "question": "(MERC42/15) If yes, please give all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Chemical name",
      "column_order": 8,
      "row_id": "1708421856107x309955773281075200",
      "answer": "Polyacrylic acid sodium salt"
    },
    {
      "question": "(MERC42/15) If yes, please give all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Restrictions and specifications",
      "column_order": 9,
      "row_id": "1708421856107x309955773281075200",
      "answer": "maximum 0.5%"
    },
    {
      "question": "(MERC42/15) If yes, please give all relevant restrictions:",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Comments",
      "column_order": 10,
      "row_id": "1708421856107x309955773281075200",
      "answer": "Product complies with the limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "MERCOSUR GMC Res. No. 02/12 - Technical regulation on the positive list of monomers, other starting substances and authorized polymers for plastic equipment in contact with food, in its current version?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not applicable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances classified as carcinogenic (C), mutagenic (M), or reprotoxic (R), according to Annex VI of the CLP Regulation (EC) No 1272/2008 as amended, in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w) or a specific concentration limit?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain SVHC substances listed in the Candidate List of Substances of Very High Concern for Authorization (Article 59 list) on the ECHA homepage, in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w)?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances subject to Authorisation according to Annex XIV of the REACH Regulation (EC) No 1907/2006 as amended in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w) or a specific concentration limit mentioned in the relevant regulation?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances subject to Restrictions according to Annex XVII of the REACH Regulation (EC) No 1907/2006 as amended in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w) or a specific concentration limit mentioned in the relevant regulation?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain priority substances listed in the Water Framework Directive (2000/60/EC) or the Directive on Environmental Quality Standards (Directive 2008/105/EC) in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w) or a specific concentration limit mentioned in the relevant regulation?\t\t\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain persistent organic pollutants (POP) in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w) or a specific concentration limit mentioned in the relevant regulation?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain more than 100 ppm (as sum) of lead, cadmium, mercury and hexavalent chromium, therefore the product can not be used in packaging material with regard to CONEG and Directive 94/62/EC on packaging and packaging waste?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain elements restricted by Standard EN 71-3, or organic contaminants as restricted by Standard EN 71-9, in its current version?\t",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances included in the California Proposition 65 list (Safe Drinking Water and Toxic Enforcement Act of 1986)?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Yes, details provided in table below."
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details of the substance identity and concentration (Drinking water)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Chemical name",
      "column_order": 1,
      "row_id": "1708447985244x395691845566070800",
      "answer": "Respirable Crystalline Silica"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details of the substance identity and concentration (Drinking water)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "CAS Number",
      "column_order": 2,
      "row_id": "1708447985244x395691845566070800",
      "answer": "14808-60-7"
    },
    {
      "question": "If yes, please provide details of the substance identity and concentration (Drinking water)",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "List table",
      "column": "Concentration",
      "column_order": 5,
      "row_id": "1708447985244x395691845566070800",
      "answer": "< 200 ppm"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances listed in the PIDSL List in concentrations exceeding the declarable limit?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain substances subject to Community rolling action plan (CoRAP) in concentrations exceeding 0.1 % (w/w) or a specific concentration limit mentioned in the relevant regulation?",
      "question_number": null,
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not intentionally added and reasonably not expected to be present above declaration limit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the delivered product and/or its production site or line have a Kosher certification?",
      "question_number": "6.1.1",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the delivered product and/or its production site or line have a Halal certification?",
      "question_number": "6.1.3",
      "response_type": "Select one",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are substances prohibited during Passover (chametz and kitniyot) intentionally added to the product? ",
      "question_number": "6.1.5",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are substances of animal origin (including dairy and dairy based ingredients) intentionally added to the product, or known contaminants in the product?",
      "question_number": "6.2.7",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is there a concern that the product contains BSE (Bovine Spongiform Encephalopathy) or TSE (Transmissible Spongiform Encephalopathies) specified risk material as defined in the Decision 97/534/EC, EMEA/410/01 and current EU legislation?",
      "question_number": "6.3.9",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is ethanol (CAS 64-17-5 ) intentionally added to the product?",
      "question_number": "6.4.10",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are food allergens as defined by Regulation (EU) No 1169/2011 intentionally added to the product, or known contaminants in the product?",
      "question_number": "6.5.12",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are food allergens as defined by US Food Allergen Labeling and Consumer Protection Act of 2004 intentionally added to the product, or known contaminants in the product?",
      "question_number": "6.5.14",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are nanomaterials as defined by EC Recommendation 2011/696/EU intentionally added to the product? ",
      "question_number": "6.6.16",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are GMOs, or substances produced from GMO but no longer containing GMO, as defined by Regulation (EU) No 1829/2003 and amendments intentionally added to the product?",
      "question_number": "6.7.18",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the product contain Mineral Oil Hydrocarbons (MOH)?",
      "question_number": "6.8.20",
      "response_type": "Dropdown",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "Not assessed"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are conflict minerals regulated by the Dodd-Frank Act or Regulation (EU) 2017/821 intentionally added to the product, or are conflict minerals used during the production of the product?",
      "question_number": "6.9.24",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are Palm Oil or Palm Kernel Oil, or components derived from Palm Oil or Palm Kernel Oil intentionally added to the product?",
      "question_number": "6.10.26",
      "response_type": "Select one Radio",
      "column": null,
      "column_order": 0,
      "row_id": null,
      "answer": "No, not intentionally added."
    }
  ]
}